# **Md. Samiur**

# Rahman



### **Contact**

#### Address:

House:07, Road:14, Sector:11, Uttara, Dhaka-1230

#### Phone:

01731312600

#### **Email:**

dev.samiur@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/samiur-rahman-dhrubo-4b154a218

## Languages

Bangla English

### **Hobbies**

- Cooking
- Sports
- Swimming
- Design

# **Summary**

I was born in a coserative family. My father's name is Md. Shafiqur Rahman, I lost him when I was 13. My mather's name is Morium Begum.I was born in Narshingdi. I have spent many years of my life in narshingdi. I have completed my Secondary School from there and my school was P.D.B. High School Ghorashal. I have completed my Higher Secondary from Milestone College which is in Dhaka. After passing my Higher Secondary School I decided to study for Computer Science and Engineering at University of Asia pacific.

## **Skill Highlights**

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

## **Experience**

Web Developer - 09/2021 to 11/2021 SoftTech It, Dhaka

Intern

**UI/UX Designer** - 06/2022 to present **Intouch It Solution**, Dhaka

### **Education**

Bachelor of Science: **Computer Science and Engineering** – 2020-present

**University of Asia Pacific** 

Higher Secondary School: **Science Group** – 2016-2018

Milestone Colleege

Secondary School: Science Group – 2006-2016

P.D.B High School